ZUNAIRA ASIF

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

CONTACT

+92 303 4774200



zunairaasif900@gmail.com



Sahiwal, Pakistan







SKILLS

HTML

React JS

CSS

Next JS

JavaScript

React Native

TypeScript

REST APIs

Tailwind CSS

Github

EDUCATION

2018-2022

BS (Computer Science)

The University of Lahore, Lahore CGPA - 3.11

2016-2018

Intermediate

Divisional Public School and Inter College (DPS), Sahiwal

LANGUAGES

English

Urdu



ABOUT

I'm an experienced Frontend React.js, Next.js and React Native developer. Passionate and motivated person that focus on delivering scalable, responsive and user-friendly applications by utilizing modern techniques and best practices. Dedicated to constantly learning and face complex challenges to enhance my skills for both personal as well as professional growth.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelance Developer

01/2024 - Present

MLPB Armory

https://dev.mlpbarmory.com/

- A blockchain project built on Next.js
- Built minting portal and email templates.
- Mostly worked on responsiveness issues and other bugs.

Finarch

https://finarch.co/

- · An architect website developed using React.js
- Used MUI for responsive and flexible design.
- Worked with integrating API's.

Ghoomo Phiroo Pakistan

https://gpp.codeminer.co/

- Developed an admin panel for a Travel Agency using React.js
- Integrated API's.

AltCode Labs

10/2022 - 12/2023

AltCode Labs

https://www.altcodelabs.com/

- Developed company's website in Next.js
- Worked with MUI for flexible design.
- Implemented 3D animations using Framer motion and Sketchfab.

Fitcy Health

https://fitcyhealth.com/

- Fitcy health is a **React.js** Web App serves as Mental Health Care platform.
- Implemented all API's.
- Fixed many UI bugs using Grommet library.